# JONATHAN S. COOPER

1989 Grant Ave apt. 211, Ogden, UT 84401 | (385)215-4747 |

Website: <a href="https://jcoops22.github.io/portfolio/">https://jcoops22.github.io/portfolio/</a>

JCooper232074@gmail.com

### **SUMMARY**

Motivated professional with excellent interpersonal skills. General knowledge of various Windows/Mac operating system's settings and use. Familiar with various front and back end programming languages including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, NodeJS and AJAX. Thrives in team-oriented environments and adapts well to the use of new software and technology. More than 3 years of technical support experience, managing software and windows environments. Over six years of experience in various other customer service settings.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### 04/2018 -Present

**Support Tech 3 Specialty Dept.**, Henry Schein Practice Solutions, American Fork, UT

- Answer inbound calls, providing high level software support for Specialty Vision software.
- Make outbound phone calls to follow up with escalated customers.
- Perform system analysis, installation, and setup of new Specialty Vision software and 3rd party applications/devices for integration with the software.
- Assist callers with questions regarding functions and features of the product.

#### 01/2016-04/2018

# Support Tech 2, Henry Schein Practice Solutions, American Fork, UT

- Provide timely customer service and innovative solutions for patrons of Dentrix Core Practice Management Software.
- Periodically serve as mentor to other phone technicians for over a year since achieving Support Tech 2 designation.
- · Efficiently navigate knowledgebase resources for more complex matters
- Implement proper troubleshooting techniques and processes for the current issue.
- · Educate callers when appropriate to avoid repeat inquiries.

#### 07/2015-12/31 /15

# Licensed Health Insurance Agent, Connexion Point, Salt Lake City, UT

- · Promptly assist clients on inbound calls with healthcare decisions.
- · Research and answer questions for prospective members.
- · Enroll callers into Medicare health insurance plans.

## 03/2012-03/20 15

Veneer Dept. Operator, Milgard Windows and Doors, Tacoma, WA

- · Efficiently produce quality veneered parts to meet production needs.
- Provide daily pass-down emails of shift performance to supervisors and management.
- Organize and lead team efforts to meet daily production quotas and maintain department order and cleanliness.

## **EDUCATION**

2015-present	IT Systems Analyst LDSBC, Salt Lake City, UT
2020-present	Dev Point Labs FullStack Web Development Bootcamp
2019-present	udemy.com Courses in Node.js, JavaScript, ReactJS, VueJS
2018	udemy.com Full Stack Developer Course
2017	treehouse.com Front End Developer Courses
2016	Test Out Microsoft Windows Server 2008/2012 Certification
2015-2015	Radiography, Salt Lake Community College, Salt Lake City, UT